Patryk Ptasiński

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PERSONAL DATA

PLACE OF BIRTH: Warsaw, Poland

Age: 27 years old

PHONE: (+48) 510 355 151 EMAIL: resume@ipepe.pl HOMEPAGE: www.ipepe.pl

Gітнив: @ipepe

Summary

Educated and experienced software engineer with broad knowledge in the field of computer science. Working in IT for almost 10 years and interested in computers since childhood. Worked on wide range of technologies and architectures like desktop, mobile and web applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2018- WebGL Developer/Lead Ruby Developer at Skriware

Responsible for creating advanced Three.js based online 3d models editor. Also did monitoring and maintenance for medium Rails application related to 3D Printing and IOT Devices. Full Stack development: Three.js, Ruby on Rails, NodeJS, ActionCable, PostgreSQL and Redis. Related: Azure, Capistrano, Integration, AirBrake (Errbit), Monitoring and GitLab.

2017 Lead Ruby Developer at **DAFTCODE SP. Z O.O.**

Responsible for planning, estimating and distributing work in a team, architecture and quality of code for medium Rails application. Full Stack development: Bootstrap, Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, Redis and Elasticsearch. Related: Kanbanery, Capistrano, Integration, AirBrake (Errbit), Monitoring and GitLab.

2015-2016 | Lead Ruby Developer at In4mates sp. z o.o. sp.k.

Lead developer in a big project related to the accounting. Managed team of 5 developers. Responsible for architecture, maintenance, deployment - whole system development life cycle. Full Stack development: Bootstrap, EmberJS, Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL and more. Related: Jenkins, Redmine, Capistrano, Docker, Vagrant, Integration, Monitoring and GitLab.

2012-2014 Systems Administrator and T2 Helpdesk at Operator Gazociągów Przesyłowych GAZ-SYSTEM S.A.

Performed second level on-site Helpdesk. Administrator of packages, applications and compliance for SCCM (2500 workstations) and on-site Aactive Directory managment (600 users and computers). Related: DevOps, Zabbix, PowerShell, VBScript, Acronis, Hardware Inventory, SLA, Microsoft Deployment Toolkit.

2012 | 24x7 Helpline Support at **Digital Virgo SA**

Responsible for supporting Paid SMS Gateway and part-time Helpdesk Support. Related: DevOps, SLA, Linux, Nagios, Scripting, Hardware Inventory and Software Lincesing.

Outsourced Systems Administrator and Helpdesk at Synergia Polska
Responsible for the infrastructure of multiple client companies. Developed multiple
small tools and applications in Java and C-Sharp. Related: SLA, Monitoring, VNC,
DevOps, Hardware and Software Technical Support.

2010 Junior OpenERP Developer and Helpdesk Support at LACAN Technologies Sp. z o.o.

Created multiple OpenERP modules. Performed duties as Secondary Systems Administrator and resolved Helpdesk tickets. Related: SLA, DevOps, Spiceworks, Monitoring, VNC, Python and MySQL.

EDUCATION

2012-2017 | Engineer degree in The Faculty of Information Technology,

Polish-Japanese Academy Of Information Technology Part time studies | Speciality: Networks of Mobile Devices Thesis: "Urban navigation based on WIFI location data"

Advisor: dr. inż. Michał Tomaszewski

Related: Ruby On Rails, Big data, WIFI, Android, Geolocation, Post-

GIS

2008-2011 | Secondary Education,

Academic High School under supervision of Polish-Japanese

Academy Of Information Technology

Speciality: Information Technology

Related: Java, SQL, UML

LANGUAGES

Polish: Mothertongue

ENGLISH: Fluent JAPANEESE: Beginner

Computer Skills

Basic: Python, Data Science, Arduino, Raspberry PI, iOS Development

Intermediate: Linux - Ubuntu Family, Git, Local Network Configuration, Windows and Linux

Network File Sharing and Backup, jQuery, Bootstrap CSS, Android Development, Web Crawling, Reverse Engineering and Hardware

Advanced: Ruby on Rails, JavaScript and PostgreSQL

Interests and Activities

Published multiple open source projects and libraries. Hacktoberfest Participant. Indie games developer. Cars and motorcycles enthusiast. Driving licence since the age of 16 with the result of 200'000+ kilometres driven to date. Rebuilt several two-stroke engines for sport/racing use. Currently exploring 3D Printing combined with microcontrollers and single board computers in areas like IoT, robotics and automation.

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the Personal Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997, consolidated text: Journal of Laws 2016, item 922 as amended.